[
    {
        "id": "1",
        "question": "The more you code, the more of me there is. I may be gone for now but you can‚Äôt get rid of me forever. What am I?",
        "answer": "A bug",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "id": "2",
        "question": "I‚Äôm a language for everything yet I have no real identity of my own. Good luck trying to compile me. What am I?",
        "answer": "Pseudocode",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "id": "3",
        "question": "As a developer I‚Äôm your eyes, showing you the result of your code in your language of choice. What am I?",
        "answer": "A print statement",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "id": "4",
        "question": "I‚Äôm fundamental and used to build larger structures. While you‚Äôll find many different kinds of me, we all just mess with information in different ways. What am I?",
        "answer": "A data structure",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "As a developer, you usually get mad at me because I complain a lot, although I‚Äôm usually right. What am I?",
        "answer": "A compiler",
        "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "I‚Äôm sent before I‚Äôm ready, I‚Äôll break before you know it and you can‚Äôt find me many places. What am I?",
        "answer": "A beta release",
        "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "I‚Äôm a simple thing, nothing special. While I have many cousins we‚Äôre all very similar because we set your project up. What am I?",
        "answer": "A configuration file",
        "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
        "id": "8",
        "question": " I‚Äôm pretty focused so I don‚Äôt do too much. However whatever you wish is my command. What am I?",
        "answer": "A command",
        "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "I catch you and your teammates when you fall and I can be you in a pinch. What am I?",
        "answer": "A product/project manager",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "I‚Äôm your ‚Äúwaiter‚Äù for information. What I am?",
        "answer": "A server",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "I come small, as small as you can get in fact. With many well-thought-out versions of me I bring stability. What am I?",
        "answer": "A unit test",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "You make me often and you‚Äôre always messing with me by pushing and pulling me all the time. Don‚Äôt you have any manners üò†üò§? What am I?",
        "answer": "Code",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "I‚Äôm a shape shifter. You could call me someone who could possess multiple qualities but only has one set of them at any given time. What am I?",
        "answer": "Polymorphism",
        "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "I‚Äôm a red and black structure and often forgotten about after learned. Although you almost always use a different color of me for Christmas. What am I?",
        "answer": "A red-black tree",
        "difficulty": "extremely-hard"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "I have a pulse but no heart, a brain but can‚Äôt think and while I can sleep, I usually don‚Äôt stay asleep for long? What am I?",
        "answer": "A CPU",
        "difficulty": "extremely-hard"
    }
]